[
  {
    "id":1,
    "question": "Answer to the Ultimate Question of Life, the Universe, and Everything?",
    "answer": "42",
    "type": "SA"
  },
  {
    "id":2,
    "question": "Which comes first hen or egg?",
    "answer": "egg",
    "type": "SA"
  },
  {
    "id":3,
    "question": "(yes/no))Do you love this course?",
    "answer": "yes",
    "type": "SA"
  },
  {
    "id":4,
    "question": "Which is your favorite course ever?",
    "answer": "SER321",
    "type": "SA"
  },
  {
    "id":5,
    "question": "Who is the best instructor ever?",
    "answer": "Mehlhase",
    "type": "SA"
  },
  {
    "id":6,
    "question": "What is ASU best at?",
    "answer": "Innovation",
    "type": "SA"
  },
  {
    "id":7,
    "question": "(true/false) UDP means handing over data with a handshake?",
    "answer": "false",
    "type": "SA"
  },
  {
    "id":8,
    "question": "(true/false) TCP means just throwing over the data not caring if it arrives?",
    "answer": "false",
    "type": "SA"
  },
  {
    "id":9,
    "question": "(true/false) HTTP is the protocol of the Web?",
    "answer": "true",
    "type": "SA"
  },
  {
    "id":10,
    "question": "(yes/no) You absolutly love what you learn in this class?",
    "answer": "yes",
    "type": "SA"
  },
  {
    "id":11,
    "question": "(yes/no) Will you fill out the end of year evaluation?",
    "answer": "yes",
    "type": "SA"
  },
  {
    "id":12,
    "question": "(yes/no) JSON is easier to read than a bytestream?",
    "answer": "yes",
    "type": "SA"
  }
]
